var questions=[
    {  "question":"Which of the following operators can be applied on structure variables?",
        "option1":"Equality comparison ( == )", 
        "option2":"Assignment ( = )",
        "option3":"Both of the above",
        "option4":"None of the above",
        "answer":"2",

    },
{  "question":"What is the use of #pragma once?",
        "option1":"Used in a header file to avoid its inclusion more than once.", 
        "option2":"Used to avoid multiple declarations of same variable.",
        "option3":"Used in a c file to include a header file at least once.",
        "option4":"Used to avoid assertions",
        "answer":"1",

    },
{  "question":"f only one memory location is to be reserved for a class variable, no matter how many objects are instantiated, then the variable should be declared as ",
        "option1":"static", 
        "option2":"register",
        "option3":"extern",
        "option4":"volatile",
        "answer":"1",
},
{  "question":"The following statement in C int (*f())[ ]declares",
        "option1":"a function returning a pointer to an array of integer", 
        "option2":"a function returning an array of pointers to integers",
        "option3":"array of functions returning pointers to integers",
        "option4":"None of the above",
        "answer":"1",

    },
    {  "question":"In _______, the bodies of the two loops are merged together to form a single loop provided that they do not make any references to each other.",
        "option1":"Loop unrolling", 
        "option2":"Strength reduction",
        "option3":"Loop jamming",
        "option4":"Loop concatenation",
        "answer":"3",

    },
    {  "question":"Given that x = 7.5, j = -1.0, n = 1.0, m = 2.0 the value of - - x + j == x>n> = m is: ",
        "option1":"0", 
        "option2":"1",
        "option3":"2",
        "option4":"3",
        "answer":"1",

    },
    {  "question":"The translator which performs macro calls expansion is called: ",
        "option1":"Macro processor", 
        "option2":"Micro pre - processor",
        "option3":"Macro pre - processor",
        "option4":"Dynamic Linker",
        "answer":"3",

    },
    {  "question":"A one dimensional array A has indices 1....75. Each element is a string and takes up three memory words. The array is stored at location 1120 decimal. The starting address of A[49] is",
        "option1":"1265", 
        "option2":"1267",
        "option3":"1266",
        "option4":"1264",
        "answer":"4",

    },
    {  "question":"Which one of the following is correct for overloaded functions in C++ ?",
        "option1":"Compiler sets up a separate function for every definition of function.", 
        "option2":"Compiler does not set up a separate function for every definition of function.",
        "option3":"Overloaded functions cannot handle different types of objects. ",
        "option4":"Overloaded functions cannot have same number of arguments.",
        "answer":"1",

    },
    {  "question":"If n has 3, then the statement a[++n]=n++;",
        "option1":"assigns 3 to a[5]", 
        "option2":"assigns 4 to a[5]",
        "option3":"assigns 4 to a[4]",
        "option4":"what is assigned is compiler dependent",
        "answer":"4",

    }
]
